<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Register for the 2016 OK State Meeting</title>
      <link>/news/2016/08/register-for-the-2016-ok-state-meeting</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/08/register-for-the-2016-ok-state-meeting</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;width:100%; text-align:left;&#34; &gt;&lt;iframe  src=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/2016-zeta-phi-beta-sorority-inc-oklahoma-state-leadership-meeting-tickets-26812041538?ref=eweb&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;1000&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; vspace=&#34;0&#34; hspace=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;5&#34; marginwidth=&#34;5&#34; scrolling=&#34;auto&#34; allowtransparency=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;font-family:Helvetica, Arial; font-size:10px; padding:5px 0 5px; margin:2px; width:100%; text-align:left;&#34; &gt;&lt;a class=&#34;powered-by-eb&#34; style=&#34;color: #dddddd; text-decoration: none;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://www.eventbrite.com/l/registration-online/&#34;&gt;Powered by Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adellaide Heard</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2016/07/adellaide-heard</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 13:56:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2016/07/adellaide-heard</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to Adellaide Dee Heard for winning the Essay Contest in the Miss Plus America Pageant!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting things done: the zeta way</title>
      <link>/news/2016/07/getting-things-done-the-zeta-way</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/07/getting-things-done-the-zeta-way</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;zeta-business:0864e9fe5a1a9be5bef2837b08ff1d86&#34;&gt;Zeta Business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are fiscal year-end reports a pain?  Flagging communication making your upcoming calendar look thin? Get your house in order with these helpful tips!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reports made easy.&lt;/strong&gt;  Create your year-end report at the beginning of the year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think about it - you create a written report every month and present it to your chapter.  Take that monthly report and copy its contents into your EOY (end of year) report as you create them. Literally your final report will write itself!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use the right tools to get the job done.&lt;/strong&gt; Microsoft Office has its proper place, but engaging business focused technologies can increase your effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Need RSVP&amp;rsquo;s?&lt;/strong&gt;  Try Facebook events, or Eventbrite for your next big thing.  Just need a meeting - Google Plus events might be a better bet, you can create a video Hangout and have rsvp automatically added to a google calendar.  For physical locations, you can have pictures auto-upload from attendees phones and get that scrapbook content ready!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing projects via email?&lt;/strong&gt;  Anyone who has ever sent, or been on the receiving end of a &amp;laquo;reply-all&amp;raquo; can tell you email is not always good for project management.  That Facebook group is all well and good, but have you ever noticed that the most recently used post floats to the top and pushes other, newer updates down?  Embrace team business focused tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://trello.com&#34;&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; (project management), &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.com&#34;&gt;Slack&lt;/a&gt; (team chat), &lt;a href=&#34;https://asana.com&#34;&gt;Asana&lt;/a&gt; (task management).  All of these programs offer both free and premium features for your next committee project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Still writing that report?&lt;/strong&gt;  Try writing a more collaborative report in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/drive/&#34;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt;.  Invite your committee and you can all edit the same document in real-time!  Google documents automatically saves your version history!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state meeting 2016</title>
      <link>/event/2016/07/state-meeting-2016</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/event/2016/07/state-meeting-2016</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;saturday-october-29-2016:6a41878f6d886b26c478dcf09675c49d&#34;&gt;Saturday, October 29, 2016&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Location: Langston University — Langston, OK — Ag Building&lt;br /&gt;
Registration: 8:00am – 8:45am&lt;br /&gt;
Business Session: &lt;strong&gt;9:00am&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early registration: $30&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
August 1, 2016 - October 1, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular registration: $40&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
October 2, 2016- October 15, 2016&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34;&gt;Download the Flyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;No on-site registration&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the Date for the 2016 State Meeting</title>
      <link>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorors get ready to attend the 2016 Oklahoma State meeting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34;&gt;Download the Flyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Save the Date Flyer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the Date for the 2016 State Meeting</title>
      <link>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 07:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorors get ready to attend the 2016 Oklahoma State meeting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34;&gt;Download the Flyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Save the Date Flyer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>74th Midwestern Regional Conference Recap</title>
      <link>/news/2016/06/74th-midwestern-regional-conference-recap</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/06/74th-midwestern-regional-conference-recap</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We all had an amazing experience at regionals. It’s truly an honor to be in the presence of Friend Wright. I appreciate the workshops that were presented by Friend Hull, Friend Sadler, and Amica Garrett. We obtained knowledge on communication, being a service to others, and taking pride in our colors. I was pleased to learn how passionate Friend Hull and Sadler are for Amicae. I can best describe them as nurturing us, grooming us to become better women, and emphasizing how sacred being a part of the blue and white family is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To all of my Zeta friends, thank you for your warm welcoming. We embrace your hugs, the love you show through your smile, and your kind words. Most of all, our Zeta friends always treated us as equals; allowing our voice to be heard. I, Shayla Beard, and Quinetta Nelson are blessed to be a member of Zeta Amicae Auxiliary. The 74th Annual Midwestern Regional Leadership Conference will be cherished for a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lillian marigny</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2015/12/lillian-marigny</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2015/12/lillian-marigny</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today Oklahoma Zetas mourn the loss of our beloved sister, Lillian Marigny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Marigny served the sorority in many capacities and on many levels, including Midwestern Regional Director.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was a true trailblazer within our sisterhood and will be truly missed. Our thoughts and prayers are with her family during this time of bereavement.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>adopt-a-street sign unveiling and street cleanup</title>
      <link>/event/2015/09/adopt-a-street-sign-unveiling-and-street-cleanup</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/event/2015/09/adopt-a-street-sign-unveiling-and-street-cleanup</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lola parker dean</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2015/01/lola-parker-dean</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2015/01/lola-parker-dean</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In 1932, Soror Lola Dean began attending Langston University in Langston, Oklahoma, and obtained her teaching certificate within 2 years and then began teaching. In the late 1930&amp;rsquo;s, she returned to Langston University to complete her Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree and became a Zeta by way of Lambda Alpha Chapter. During a recent interview, Soror Dean stated that was drawn to Zeta because of the work that she saw the young women do around the campus and she appreciated what they stood for. Soror Dean began teaching at Harrison Chapel School and then moved to Porter, Oklahoma, where she served as principal at the all black Porter school. When integration began to take shape, all of the African American teachers were fired and all the black schools were closed in Muskogee county. As a result, Soror Dean filed a lawsuit, suing the district for her job. She won that lawsuit and shortly thereafter additional black teachers were hired at schools throughout the district.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Dean has been quoted saying &amp;laquo;My greatest contribution to education is that I taught my kids to study and to do what it took to get them where they wanted to go. Some of them didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to work, stay up late, and &amp;lsquo;burn the midnight oil&amp;rsquo; or to do whatever it took to make it. Hard work never killed anybody; otherwise, I would have been gone a long time ago,&amp;raquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the 1970&amp;rsquo;s, Soror Lola Dean served as the Basileus of Alpha Iota Zeta in Tulsa, Oklahoma.  In addition to the local offices that Soror Dean held, she also served the sisterhood on the state and Midwestern Regional level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Dean was a longtime member and diligent work at Mount Bethel Baptist Church and within the communities of Tullahassee, Porter, and Wagoner. Soror Dean and her husband were not blessed with children, but she has stated in the past that she always had children around her and she helped to raise many children over the years. Every year, Soror Dean would personally take a group of youth from the surrounding area on a trip each summer to expose them to other areas in the US. During the summer of 2013, Soror Dean took a group of youth from the community to Seattle, Washington. Unfortunately, she became ill in the spring of 2014 and was unable to take the group to Atlanta as planned that summer.  She was inducted into the Oklahoma African American Educators Hall of Fame in September of 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Lola Parker Dean recently became a member of the Phi Beta Zeta chapter in Tulsa, Oklahoma, and had been making plans to attend the 73rd Midwestern Regional Conference. Unfortunately, Soror Dean fell ill in December and transitioned to her eternal home in January. Soror Lola Parker Dean has joined our other triumphant Sorors at the Grand Boule’ in the sky. We will forever remember the contributions that Soror Dean made to our sisterhood.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chi Zeta &amp; Lambda Alpha</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2014/05/chi-zeta--lambda-alpha</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2014/05/chi-zeta--lambda-alpha</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;undergraduate-chapter-of-the-year:d3aaa7fa11b9c4e1e6011a58497f4c6c&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Chapter of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boasting a delegation made up entirely of 1st time attendees, Basileus Lashonda Taylor and her fellow delegates worked hard before, during and after the conference.  Their undergraduate advisor, Soror LaTonya Anderson and the Beta Phi Zeta Graduate Chapter President, Soror Curtesia Smith, were present to witness these young ladies receive this honor.  They also competed and won the stroll off competition that was hosted by the Midwestern Region.  Congratulations to the sorors who were in attendance and those that were unable attend the leadership conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;graduate-chapter-of-the-year:d3aaa7fa11b9c4e1e6011a58497f4c6c&#34;&gt;Graduate Chapter of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chi Zeta Chapter of Oklahoma City was presented with the Graduate Chapter of the Year plaque.  Having been active for over 50 years, the chapter was presented with two other awards for the 2013 Top Teams within the region for their fundraising efforts with the March of Dimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Outstanding State of Oklahoma is proud to have two of their chapters take home such high honors!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greetings from oklahoma state</title>
      <link>/news/2014/04/state-director-woody-greetings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2014/04/state-director-woody-greetings</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-the-website-of-zeta-phi-beta-sorority-inc-outstanding-state-of-oklahoma:f0bec1d869e1df63516d1bfc946676e3&#34;&gt;Welcome to the website of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. – Outstanding State of Oklahoma!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am delighted to extend greetings to you on behalf of the Sorors, Amicae and Archonettes in this great state. This web page is our way of communication with members in our state as well as sharing our legacy of service to others. As you peruse our website, you will find evidence that the Zeta family in the State of Oklahoma continues the legacy of Scholarship, Service, Sisterly Love, and Finer Womanhood that began in 1920 with founding of the sorority; and in 1927 when the first undergraduate chapter was chartered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The State of Oklahoma is comprised of dedicated and hardworking members of the sorority who are committed to bettering our local communitites, our state, our country, and the world. We display this commitment through programming such as ZHOPE (Zetas Helping Other People Excel), our Stork&amp;rsquo;s Nests, and our long-lasting partnerships with the March of Dimes and the American Cancer Society. Through countless hours of community service and donations, Zetas are definately making a difference!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a soror in search of a Zeta home or would like to learn more about becoming a member of our illustrious organization, please contact us and someone will contact you with more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you for taking the time to visit our website and we hope that the site has served its purpose for providing you information about Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. and our presence in Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sisterly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Soror Artisha Harris-Woody&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Oklahoma State Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xi Nu Zeta</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2013/11/xi-nu-zeta</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2013/11/xi-nu-zeta</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Xi Nu Zeta Chapter of Midwest City, OK was charted in 1989.  Reactivated in 2004, the chapter participates in several national philanthropical community programs, as well as hosting local initiatives, including an Annual Community Picnic where they collect and disburse school supplies and award a scholarship.  They also host a group fitness activity - Strides for Your Heart and the Pajamas, Books and Joy reading program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror RJ Lewis and her committee did a beautiful job of putting together their scrapbook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shelita jones</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2013/10/shelita-jones</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2013/10/shelita-jones</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Soror Shelita Jones is a Soror’s Soror. Her smile, positive attitude, and spirit of volunteerism is contagious. She lends a hand to anyone in need. She is eager to learn more and more about Zeta and exhibits all the qualities that our beloved sorority was founded upon. She has been a member since 2010 and within that time she has held positions such as the Xi Nu Zeta chapter Sunshine chairperson, the Xi Nu Zeta chapter Tamias-Grammateus, and ZΦB State of Oklahoma ZHOPE coordinator. She was also named Xi Nu Zeta’s chapter member of the year for the 2012-2013 fiscal year. She has volunteered countless hours to her local chapter projects as well as the state’s initiatives and events. She has regular attendance at local meetings and she has also attended several state meetings as well as regional conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Jones is an true asset to Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. and the sky is the limit on the potential she has for future leadership positions within the organization. I am proud to not only call her my Soror, but my friend as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sisterly Submitted,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Soror Keisha Driskell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Basileus – Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Xi Nu Zeta Chapter&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lambda Alpha</title>
      <link>/spotlight/2013/09/lambda-alpha</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spotlight/2013/09/lambda-alpha</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chartered December 11, 1937 at Langston University in Langston, OK; Zeta was the first national sorority established on Langston’s campus. At that time, it was comprised of both undergraduate and graduate women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In April 2013 Lambda Alpha Chapter won Oklahoma State&amp;rsquo;s Membership Focus Initiative, by welcoming 15 young ladies to the sorority, bringing their total chapter membership to 21!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations ladies!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>