<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 14:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>getting things done: the zeta way</title>
      <link>/news/2016/07/getting-things-done-the-zeta-way</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 14:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/07/getting-things-done-the-zeta-way</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;zeta-business:0864e9fe5a1a9be5bef2837b08ff1d86&#34;&gt;Zeta Business&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are fiscal year-end reports a pain?  Flagging communication making your upcoming calendar look thin? Get your house in order with these helpful tips!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reports made easy.&lt;/strong&gt;  Create your year-end report at the beginning of the year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think about it - you create a written report every month and present it to your chapter.  Take that monthly report and copy its contents into your EOY (end of year) report as you create them. Literally your final report will write itself!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use the right tools to get the job done.&lt;/strong&gt; Microsoft Office has its proper place, but engaging business focused technologies can increase your effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Need RSVP&amp;rsquo;s?&lt;/strong&gt;  Try Facebook events, or Eventbrite for your next big thing.  Just need a meeting - Google Plus events might be a better bet, you can create a video Hangout and have rsvp automatically added to a google calendar.  For physical locations, you can have pictures auto-upload from attendees phones and get that scrapbook content ready!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing projects via email?&lt;/strong&gt;  Anyone who has ever sent, or been on the receiving end of a &amp;laquo;reply-all&amp;raquo; can tell you email is not always good for project management.  That Facebook group is all well and good, but have you ever noticed that the most recently used post floats to the top and pushes other, newer updates down?  Embrace team business focused tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://trello.com&#34;&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; (project management), &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.com&#34;&gt;Slack&lt;/a&gt; (team chat), &lt;a href=&#34;https://asana.com&#34;&gt;Asana&lt;/a&gt; (task management).  All of these programs offer both free and premium features for your next committee project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Still writing that report?&lt;/strong&gt;  Try writing a more collaborative report in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/drive/&#34;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt;.  Invite your committee and you can all edit the same document in real-time!  Google documents automatically saves your version history!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the Date for the 2016 State Meeting</title>
      <link>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 07:18:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/06/save-the-date-for-the-2016-state-meeting</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sorors get ready to attend the 2016 Oklahoma State meeting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34;&gt;Download the Flyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2016/06/2016std_full_size.png&#34; alt=&#34;Save the Date Flyer&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>74th Midwestern Regional Conference Recap</title>
      <link>/news/2016/06/74th-midwestern-regional-conference-recap</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2016/06/74th-midwestern-regional-conference-recap</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We all had an amazing experience at regionals. It’s truly an honor to be in the presence of Friend Wright. I appreciate the workshops that were presented by Friend Hull, Friend Sadler, and Amica Garrett. We obtained knowledge on communication, being a service to others, and taking pride in our colors. I was pleased to learn how passionate Friend Hull and Sadler are for Amicae. I can best describe them as nurturing us, grooming us to become better women, and emphasizing how sacred being a part of the blue and white family is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To all of my Zeta friends, thank you for your warm welcoming. We embrace your hugs, the love you show through your smile, and your kind words. Most of all, our Zeta friends always treated us as equals; allowing our voice to be heard. I, Shayla Beard, and Quinetta Nelson are blessed to be a member of Zeta Amicae Auxiliary. The 74th Annual Midwestern Regional Leadership Conference will be cherished for a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greetings from Zeta Phi Beta sorority, inc.-oklahoma state</title>
      <link>/news/2014/04/state-director-woody-greetings</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/2014/04/state-director-woody-greetings</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-the-website-of-zeta-phi-beta-sorority-inc-outstanding-state-of-oklahoma:f0bec1d869e1df63516d1bfc946676e3&#34;&gt;Welcome to the website of Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. – Outstanding State of Oklahoma!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am delighted to extend greetings to you on behalf of the Sorors, Amicae and Archonettes in this great state. This web page is our way of communication with members in our state as well as sharing our legacy of service to others. As you peruse our website, you will find evidence that the Zeta family in the State of Oklahoma continues the legacy of Scholarship, Service, Sisterly Love, and Finer Womanhood that began in 1920 with founding of the sorority; and in 1927 when the first undergraduate chapter was chartered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The State of Oklahoma is comprised of dedicated and hardworking members of the sorority who are committed to bettering our local communitites, our state, our country, and the world. We display this commitment through programming such as ZHOPE (Zetas Helping Other People Excel), our Stork&amp;rsquo;s Nests, and our long-lasting partnerships with the March of Dimes and the American Cancer Society. Through countless hours of community service and donations, Zetas are definately making a difference!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a soror in search of a Zeta home or would like to learn more about becoming a member of our illustrious organization, please contact us and someone will contact you with more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you for taking the time to visit our website and we hope that the site has served its purpose for providing you information about Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. and our presence in Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sisterly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Soror Artisha Harris-Woody&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Oklahoma State Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>