<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zeta spotlight on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</title>
    <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/categories/zeta-spotlight/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zeta spotlight on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:16:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://zphiboklahoma.org/categories/zeta-spotlight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>shelita jones</title>
      <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/10/shelita-jones</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2013 15:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/10/shelita-jones</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Soror Shelita Jones is a Soror’s Soror. Her smile, positive attitude, and spirit of volunteerism is contagious. She lends a hand to anyone in need. She is eager to learn more and more about Zeta and exhibits all the qualities that our beloved sorority was founded upon. She has been a member since 2010 and within that time she has held positions such as the Xi Nu Zeta chapter Sunshine chairperson, the Xi Nu Zeta chapter Tamias-Grammateus, and ZΦB State of Oklahoma ZHOPE coordinator. She was also named Xi Nu Zeta’s chapter member of the year for the 2012-2013 fiscal year. She has volunteered countless hours to her local chapter projects as well as the state’s initiatives and events. She has regular attendance at local meetings and she has also attended several state meetings as well as regional conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror Jones is an true asset to Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. and the sky is the limit on the potential she has for future leadership positions within the organization. I am proud to not only call her my Soror, but my friend as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sisterly Submitted,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Soror Keisha Driskell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Basileus – Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Xi Nu Zeta Chapter&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>marian martin</title>
      <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/07/marian-martin</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 16:36:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/07/marian-martin</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have known Soror Martin for about a decade now. The phrase that comes to mind when I think of her?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Zeta calls, we’ll answer one and all&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most recently, I was called upon to collect and document the history of the state. I requested that each chapter submit a representative&lt;br /&gt;
to the committee. Despite being the outgoing chapter historian for Chi Zeta, Soror Martin went above and beyond to make certain that their historical information was as accurate as possible before relinquishing her duties. She went a step further and provided historical data for both Beta Gamma and Theta Mu Chapters as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much Soror Martin. You have truly put the “&lt;strong&gt;Z&lt;/strong&gt;” in Zeta for me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sisterly,&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;RJ Lewis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>