<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chapter spotlight on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</title>
    <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/categories/chapter-spotlight/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chapter spotlight on Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. - Oklahoma State</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://zphiboklahoma.org/categories/chapter-spotlight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Chi Zeta &amp; Lambda Alpha</title>
      <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2014/05/chi-zeta--lambda-alpha</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2014/05/chi-zeta--lambda-alpha</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;undergraduate-chapter-of-the-year:d3aaa7fa11b9c4e1e6011a58497f4c6c&#34;&gt;Undergraduate Chapter of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boasting a delegation made up entirely of 1st time attendees, Basileus Lashonda Taylor and her fellow delegates worked hard before, during and after the conference.  Their undergraduate advisor, Soror LaTonya Anderson and the Beta Phi Zeta Graduate Chapter President, Soror Curtesia Smith, were present to witness these young ladies receive this honor.  They also competed and won the stroll off competition that was hosted by the Midwestern Region.  Congratulations to the sorors who were in attendance and those that were unable attend the leadership conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;graduate-chapter-of-the-year:d3aaa7fa11b9c4e1e6011a58497f4c6c&#34;&gt;Graduate Chapter of the Year&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chi Zeta Chapter of Oklahoma City was presented with the Graduate Chapter of the Year plaque.  Having been active for over 50 years, the chapter was presented with two other awards for the 2013 Top Teams within the region for their fundraising efforts with the March of Dimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Outstanding State of Oklahoma is proud to have two of their chapters take home such high honors!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xi Nu Zeta</title>
      <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/11/xi-nu-zeta</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/11/xi-nu-zeta</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Xi Nu Zeta Chapter of Midwest City, OK was charted in 1989.  Reactivated in 2004, the chapter participates in several national philanthropical community programs, as well as hosting local initiatives, including an Annual Community Picnic where they collect and disburse school supplies and award a scholarship.  They also host a group fitness activity - Strides for Your Heart and the Pajamas, Books and Joy reading program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soror RJ Lewis and her committee did a beautiful job of putting together their scrapbook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lambda Alpha</title>
      <link>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/09/lambda-alpha</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zphiboklahoma.org/spotlight/2013/09/lambda-alpha</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chartered December 11, 1937 at Langston University in Langston, OK; Zeta was the first national sorority established on Langston’s campus. At that time, it was comprised of both undergraduate and graduate women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In April 2013 Lambda Alpha Chapter won Oklahoma State&amp;rsquo;s Membership Focus Initiative, by welcoming 15 young ladies to the sorority, bringing their total chapter membership to 21!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations ladies!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>